[{"question":"which object is bigger?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The metal cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"What is the material of the small cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"Wood"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"Marble"}],"answer":1},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small marble cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small brick cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Is the small marble cube lighter than the medium metal cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has larger friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium metal cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small concrete cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small brick cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the small marble cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium metal cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small marble cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small marble cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small brick cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the small concrete cube travel to quadrant \u2161?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2161?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the small marble cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the small marble cube collide with the small concrete cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the small marble cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The wall and the small brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small marble cube and the small brick cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The small brick cube and the small concrete cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium metal cube and the small concrete cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The wall and the small brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small marble cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The small brick cube and the small marble cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium metal cube and the wall"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Will the small brick cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0}]